Guide to the Norman Strung Papers 1966-1982
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
Norman Strung Papers
1966-1982
Montana State University Library, Merrill G. Burlingame Special Collections P.O. Box 173320 Bozeman, MT 59717-3320 United States Phone (406) 994-4242 Fax (406) 994-2851 http://www.lib.montana.edu/archives/ University Archivist spcoll@www.lib.montana.edu
Collection 987, MtBC, us
Strung, Norman
10.4 linear feet
This Norman Strung Papers are made up primarily of literary manuscripts written by Norman Strung. There are rough and final drafts of the books he wrote along with galley proofs. In addition to his feature article manuscripts is correspondence that pertains to his writings, such as acceptances and rejections of his articles. Almost all of his articles are on the subject of the outdoors.
Biographical Note
Norman Strung was born on October 21, 1941 in New York, N.Y. and married Priscilla (Sil) Hoerschgen in October, 1963. He received his B.S. from Montana State University-Bozeman that year and attended University of Montana in 1963-64. While Strung spent the majority of his career as a free-lance outdoor writer, he was also a licensed hunting and fishing guide and an instructor of English at Montana State University from 1964-67, a consultant for the Hunting and Fishing Library and Fish America Foundation, and the Outdoor editor for Mechanix Illustrated and an associate editor for Field and Stream. Besides writing numerous feature articles, Norman Strung also wrote or contributed to at least 15 different books: The Fisherman's Almanac, 1970 with Dan Morris; Family Fun Around the Water, 1970 also with Dan Morris; The Hunter's Almanac, 1971; Camping in Comfort, 1971, with Sil Strung; The Complete Outdoor Cookbook, (contributor), 1971, Dan and Inez Morris; Deer Hunting in North America, 1973; Spinfishing: The Complete System, 1973; Misty Mornings and Moonless Nights: A Waterfowler's Guide, 1974; Communicating the Outdoor Experience, (editor), 1975; Whitewater!, 1976, with Sam Curtis and Earl Perry; The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1977; The Complete Hunter's Catalog, 1977; To Catch a Trout, 1979; Fishing the Headwaters of the Missouri, 1981; and The Art of Hunting, 1984. Strung also published under 2 pseudonyms, "Bart Yaeger" and "Asouff Barkee" to many of the outdoor magazines. Norman Strung died at the age of 49 on October 17, 1991 at his home in Bozeman, Montana.
This collection is made up primarily of literary manuscripts written by Norman Strung. There are rough and final drafts of the books he wrote along with galley proofs. In addition to his feature article manuscripts is correspondence that pertains to his writings, such as acceptances and rejections of his articles. Almost all of his articles are on the subject of the outdoors. The material was first sorted into series and chronologically arranged thereafter, except in the case of the unpublished or date of publication unknown manuscripts. These materials are arranged alphabetically according to title.
Series 1 Book Manuscripts
Series 2 Magazine Manuscripts
Subseries 1 - Confirmed publication manuscripts
Subseries 2 - Unconfirmed publication manuscripts
Series 3 Magazines and pictures about Norman Strung
Series 4 Published articles with magazines only
This collection is open for research.
Norman and Sil Strung
Outdoor life; Outdoor writers-Montana-Bozeman
Fisheries and Wildlife; Fishing and Canning; Literature; Sports and Recreation; Water and Water Rights; Montana; Bozeman
- Book Manuscripts, Series 1
  These are all book manuscripts written by Norman Strung. These manuscripts fit into different groups, the books Norman wrote alone, the books Strung wrote with others, the books he edited and the books he just contributed an article and chapter to. The manuscripts are organized chronologically by the publication dates.
  - Fisherman's Almanac, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman (Box-folder 1/1)
    proofs
  - Fisherman's Almanac, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman (Box-folder 1/2)
    charts
  - Fisherman's Almanac, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman (Box-folder 1/3)
    outline
  - Family Fun On and Around the Water, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman, 1969 (Box-folder 1/4)
    printed draft
  - Family Fun On and Around the Water, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman, 1969 (Box-folder 1/5)
    presentation
  - Family Fun On and Around the Water, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman, 1969 (Box-folder 1/6-7)
    working copy
  - Family Fun On and Around the Water, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman, 1969 (Box-folder 2/1)
    working copy cont.
  - Family Fun On and Around the Water, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman, 1969 (Box-folder 2/2)
    final copy, p. 1-201
  - Family Fun On and Around the Water, Morris, Dan and Strung, Norman, 1969 (Box-folder 2/3)
    final copy p. 202-445
  - Camping in Comfort, Lippincott, 1971 (Box-folder 2/4)
    rough draft and paste up
  - Camping in Comfort, Lippincott, 1971 (Box-folder 2/5)
    rough draft
  - Camping in Comfort, Lippincott, 1971 (Box-folder 3/1)
    miscellaneous chapter notes and correspondence
  - The Hunter's Almanac, Macmillan, 1971 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - The Hunter's Almanac, Macmillan, 1971 (Box-folder 3/3)
    3rd copy and acceptance letter with terms
  - The Hunter's Almanac, Macmillan, 1971 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - "Where Will Our Waterfowl be in Ten Years", Winchester Hunter's Handbook, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3/5)
    p. 174-180
  - Deer Hunting in North America, 1973 (Box-folder 3/6)
    correspondence
  - Deer Hunting in North America, 1973 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Deer Hunting in North America, 1973 (Box-folder 4/1)
    4th copy
  - Deer Hunting in North America, 1973 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Spin-fishing: The System that Does It All, Strung, Norman and Rosko, Milt, April 1973 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Spin-fishing: The System that Does It All, Strung, Norman and Rosko, Milt, April 1973 (Box-folder 4/4)
    cast-off galleys of book
  - Spin-fishing: The System that Does It All, Strung, Norman and Rosko, Milt, April 1973 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Spin-fishing: The System that Does It All, Strung, Norman and Rosko, Milt, April 1973 (Box-folder 4/6-7)
  - Spin-fishing: The System that Does It All, Strung, Norman and Rosko, Milt, April 1973 (Box-folder 4/8-9)
    4th copy of final draft
  - Misty Mornings and Moonless Nights, September 1974 (Box-folder 4/10)
    manuscript
  - Misty Mornings and Moonless Nights, September 1974 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Misty Mornings and Moonless Nights, September 1974 (Box-folder 5/2)
    3rd and 4th copy
  - Misty Mornings and Moonless Nights, September 1974 (Box-folder 5/3-4)
  - Misty Mornings and Moonless Nights, September 1974 (Box-folder 5/5)
    galleys
  - Communicating the Outdoor Experience, Norman Strung - editor, 1975 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Communicating the Outdoor Experience, Norman Strung - editor, 1975 (Box-folder 6/2-3)
  - Communicating the Outdoor Experience, Norman Strung - editor, 1975 (Box-folder 6/4)
    final copy
  - "Float Camping", The Complete Book of Boat Camping, Morris, Dan, 1975 (Box-folder 6/5)
    published as a chapter in book
  - "I've Called Mule Deer Many Things But I've Never Called Them Dumb", The Experts Book of Big Game Hunting, Dave Petzal - editor, 1975 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - "Paddle Ducks", The Experts Book of Upland Bird-Waterfowl, Dave Petzal - editor, 1975 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/9)
    forward
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/10)
    food knives
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/1)
    outdoor knives
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/2)
    shop and garden knives
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/3-4)
    manuscript and illustrations
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/5)
    illustrations
  - The Cutting Edge: An Encyclopedia of Knives, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/6)
    3rd copy
  - "The Lure of the Decoy", All About Wildfowling in America, Jerome Knap - editor, 1976 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 8/2)
    Macmillian, correspondence
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 8/3)
    Macmillian, covers
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 8/4)
    Macmillian, rough draft pt. 1
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 8/5)
    Macmillian, rough draft pt. 2
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 8/6)
    Macmillian, 3rd copy pt. 1
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 8/7)
    Macmillian, 3rd copy pt. 2
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 8/8)
    Macmillian, galley proof pt. 1
  - WHITEWATER!, Strung, Norman, Curtis, Sam; and Perry, Earl, 1976 (Box-folder 9/1)
    Macmillian, galley proof pt. 2
  - "Spinning Gear for Trout", The Complete Fisherman's Catalog, Henkin, Harmon, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 9/3-7)
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/1)
    correspondence of authors
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/2)
    correspondence between editors and publishing company
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/3)
    product and company lists and addresses researched
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/5)
    layout examples
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/6)
    quotes for fillers
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/7)
    illustrations, fillers and notes
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/8)
    word tally
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/9)
    index
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/10)
    section by John Barsness
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/11)
    big game section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/12)
    black powder/collecting section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/13)
    care and repair section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/14)
    hunting handguns section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/15)
    collect and display section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/16)
    custom gun section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/17)
    plinking section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/18)
    reload section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 10/19)
    small game section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/1)
    chapter 1, big game ideas
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/2)
    U.S. exotic big game section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/3)
    final African game section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/4)
    1st original African game section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/5)
    target section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/6)
    upland game/dogs/waterfowl section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/7)
    varmint section
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 11/8)
    rough draft pt1
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 12/1)
    rough draft pt. 2
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 12/2)
    galley proofs pt. 1
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 12/3)
    galley proofs pt. 2
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 12/4)
    galley proofs pt. 3
  - The Complete Hunter's Catalog, Norman Strung - editor, Lippincott, 1977 (Box-folder 12/5)
    galley proofs index
  - Norm Strung's Pocket Guide to the Madison River, Cottonwood Press, 1979 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - To Catch a Trout, Strung, Norman, Stein and Day Publishers, 1979 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - To Catch a Trout, Strung, Norman, Stein and Day Publishers, 1979 (Box-folder 13/3)
    4th copy pt. 2
  - To Catch a Trout, Strung, Norman, Stein and Day Publishers, 1979 (Box-folder 13/4)
    original manuscript pt. 1
  - To Catch a Trout, Strung, Norman, Stein and Day Publishers, 1979 (Box-folder 13/5)
    original manuscript pt. 2
  - "The Big Sky's Neglected Bass", Bass Fishing Handbook, Lamar Underwood - editor, 1980 (Box-folder 13/6)
    published as a chapter
  - "Club Pacifico de Panama", Eppinger daredevil lure catalog, 1980 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Fishing the Headwaters of the Missouri, Strung, Norman, Mountain Press Publishing Company, 1980 (Box-folder 13/8)
    draft pt. 1
  - Fishing the Headwaters of the Missouri, Strung, Norman, Mountain Press Publishing Company, 1980 (Box-folder 13/9)
    draft pt. 2
  - "Mini Spinning for Trout", Eppinger Daredevle Catalog, 1982 (Box-folder 13/10)
  - "Knife", World Book Encyclopedia, 1982 (Box-folder 13/11)
- Magazine Manuscripts, Series 2
  Manuscripts of magazine feature articles written by Norman Strung, along with pertinent correspondence. Some manuscripts were written under several various pseudonyms for mostly sports/outdoor magazines. The other names Strung sometimes used were Bart Yaeger and Asouf Barkee. Also included are articles Norman Strung "ghostwrote" for another man by the name of Walter Cook. The articles are arranged chronologically beginning with the earliest year. Two subseries divide these articles by those whose publication can be confirmed and those whose publication is uncertain.
  - Confirmed publication manuscripts, Subseries 1
    - "The Month the Madison Goes Wild", Field and Stream, June 1966 (Box-folder 14/1)
      p. 54, no article but correspondence
    - "Frosting on the Madison", Western Outdoors, March 1967 (Box-folder 14/2)
      p. 30-31+, article and correspondence
    - "Comments from the Outside", DARE, September 1967 (Box-folder 14/3)
      p. 12+
    - "The River They Always Forget", Sports Afield, January 1968 (?) (Box-folder 14/4)
      no article but correspondence
    - "Hottest Fishing in the World", Fishing World, May/June 1968 (Box-folder 14/5)
      p. 26-28, no article but correspondence
    - "Big City Broadbill", Sports Afield, July 1968 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - "A Fly for All Seasons", Sports Afield Fishing Annual, 1969 (Box-folder 14/7)
      p. 102-108, no article but correspondence
    - "Float for First-Class Fishing", Field and Stream, June 1969 (Box-folder 14/8)
      p. 68+, article and correspondence
    - "Big Sky Pike Explosion", Sports Afield, June 1969 (Box-folder 14/9)
      p. 28+, article and correspondence
    - "Me And The Bears", Sports Afield, August 1969 (Box-folder 14/10)
      article and correspondence
    - "Wheels in the Wild (Part I)", Sports Afield, August 1969 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - "The Spinner and The Fly", Fishing World, September 1969 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - "Dam Those Browns", Sportfishing, September/October 1969 (Box-folder 14/13)
      p. 18+, article and correspondence
    - "Fun on Ice!", Fishing World, November/December 1969 (Box-folder 14/14)
      p. 22-27
    - "The Lake Where No One Gets Skunked", Sports Afield Fishing Annual, 1970 (Box-folder 14/15)
      p. 4-8
    - "Fur Bearing Trout", Field and Stream, January 1970 (Box-folder 14/16)
      p. 40+, no article but correspondence
    - "Hot Fishing in Cold Streams", Sportfishing, February 1970 (Box-folder 14/17)
      p. 34-38, article and correspondence
    - "A Fishing Guide's Dare", Sports Afield, March 1970 (Box-folder 14/18)
      p. 40+, article and correspondence
    - "How to Catch Trophy Trout", Fishing World, March/April 1970 (Box-folder 14/19)
      p. 20-25, article and correspondence
    - "The Flathead Monster - Fact or Fiction?" Sportfishing, April 1970 (Box-folder 14/20)
      p. 32+, correspondence but no article
    - "Drive-in Graylings", Field and Stream, May 1970 (Box-folder 14/21)
      p. 74+, article and correspondence
    - "A Guide to Guides", Sportfishing, May 1970 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - "Savvy that Makes Every Shot Count", Sports Afield, May 1970 (Box-folder 14/23)
      p. 74+
    - "The Delicate Grayling", Fishing World, May/June 1970 (Box-folder 14/24)
      p. 36-39
    - "Small Stream Savvy", Field and Stream, July 1970 (Box-folder 14/25)
      p. 42+, article and correspondence
    - "Wheels in the Wild (Part II)", Sports Afield, June 1970 (Box-folder 14/26)
      p. 46+, article and correspondence
    - "Underneath a Rock", Fishing World, September/October 1970 (Box-folder 14/27)
      p. 24-27, article and correspondence
    - "The Downfall of Smart Mulies", Sports Afield, October 1970 (Box-folder 14/28)
      p. 50, article and correspondence
    - "Great Dam Fishing", Sports Afield Fishing Annual, 1971 (Box-folder 14/29)
      p. 112-120, article and correspondence
    - "Lake of the Whoppers", Sports Afield Fishing Annual, 1971 (Box-folder 14/20)
      p. 106-111, article and correspondence
    - "Hunt High for Big Racks", Sports Afield Hunting Annual, 1971 (Box-folder 14/31)
      p. 21, article and correspondence
    - "Pronghorn Payoff: Tactics That Score", Sports Afield Hunting Annual, 1971 (Box-folder 14/32)
      p. 4-10, correspondence but no article
    - "I'm Always Chasing Rainbows", Fish Locator, ? 1971 (Box-folder 14/33)
    - "Rainbows at Ice-out", True's Fishing Yearbook, 1971 (Box-folder 14/34)
      p. 55-57+, article and correspondence
    - "Tackle for Traveling Light", Sportfishing, February 1971 (Box-folder 14/35)
      p. 22+, article and correspondence
    - "Prospecting for Mountain Trout" Field and Stream, March 1971 (Box-folder 14/36)
      p. 52, article and correspondence
    - "Across the River in the Steelhead", Fishing World, March/April 1971 (Box-folder 14/37)
      p. 26+
    - "Trophy Antelope: They're not that Tough", National Sportsman, April 1971 (Box-folder 14/38)
    - "Tactics for Tame Trout", Sportfishing, April 1971 (Box-folder 14/39)
      p. 16+, article and correspondence
    - "How to Hire a Big-Game Guide", Sports Afield, May 1971 (Box-folder 14/40)
      p. 63+
    - "Rotten Trout Fisherman", Fishing World, May/June 1971 (Box-folder 14/41)
      p. 38+, article and correspondence
    - "The Northerns are in", Field and Stream, November 1971 (Box-folder 15/1)
      p. 52+, article and correspondence
    - "Witness to Outrage", Sports Afield, November 1971 (Box-folder 15/2)
      p. 10-12, article and correspondence
    - "The Boat That Goes By Car", Fishing World, November/December 1971 (Box-folder 15/3)
      p. 42-46
    - "Know-How for Snow-Time Ducks", Sports Afield, December 1971 (Box-folder 15/4)
      p. 30+, article and correspondence
    - "Mountain Trout", The expert's book of freshwater fishing, 1972 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - "Camping", Americana Annual, 1972 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - "When Mulies Make Mistakes", Sports Afield Hunting Annual, 1972 (Box-folder 15/7)
      p. 26-29, article and correspondence
    - "Public Hunting and Posted Lands" Sports Afield Hunting Annual, 1972 (Box-folder 15/8)
      p. 60-62
    - "Snowmobile Safari for Cutthroats", True's Fishing Yearbook, 1972 (Box-folder 15/9)
      p. 19+, article and correspondence
    - "First You Wave a Black Flag!", True's Hunting Yearbook, 1972 (Box-folder 15/10)
      p. 76+, article and correspondence
    - "How to Come Unstuck", Fishing World, January/February 1972 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - "The Careful Coexistence", Snotrack, February 1972 (Box-folder 15/12)
      p. 12-14
    - "Take a 'Companion' to Dinner", Field and Stream, February 1972 (Box-folder 15/13)
      p. 102-104, article and correspondence
    - "Wrestling the Wild Hog", Sports Afield, February 1972 (Box-folder 15/14)
      p. 71+, article and correspondence
    - "Quail Southern Style", Field and Stream, March 1972 (Box-folder 15/15)
      p. 73+, article and correspondence
    - "A Definitive Study of the Working Worm", Sportsfishing, March 1972 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - "When Fido Needs a Friend", Field and Stream, April 1972 (Box-folder 15/17)
      p. 230+, article and correspondence
    - "Trophy Trout on a Nightmare River", Sports Afield, April 1972 (Box-folder 15/18)
      p. 49+, article and correspondence
    - "One More River to Cross...Off", Sports Afield, May 1972 (Box-folder 15/19)
      p. 12-14, article and correspondence
    - "A Walk on the Wild Side", Sports Afield, May 1972 (Box-folder 15/20)
      p. 33+, article and correspondence
    - "Camping Nature's Way", Grolier, May 17, 1972 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - "Big Sky Bass", Sports Afield, June 1972 (Box-folder 15/22)
      p. 57+, article and correspondence
    - "An Eye on the Sky", Sports Afield, July 1972 (Box-folder 15/23)
      p. 48, article and correspondence
    - "The Fine Art of Decoying a Duck", Sports Afield, November 1972 (Box-folder 15/24)
    - "Hunting for Range Pike", Fishing World, September/October 1972 (Box-folder 15/25)
      p. 26, correspondence and article
    - "Not to Catch a 'cuda", Fishing World, September/October 1972 (Box-folder 15/26)
      p. 28+
    - "Best Shooting in Montana", Outdoor Life, December 1972 (Box-folder 15/27)
      p. 42+
    - "Fool'Em with Floaters", Sports Afield Fishing Annual, 1973 (Box-folder 15/28)
      p. 32-36, article and correspondence
    - "Pronghorns are Oddballs", Sports Afield Hunting Annual, 1973 (Box-folder 16/1)
      p. 74-77, article and correspondence
    - "Terrain Tactics Fool Smart Mulies", Sports Afield Hunting Annual, 1973 (Box-folder 16/2)
      p. 46-51, article and correspondence
    - "Florida's Wilderness Whoppers", True's Fishing Yearbook, 1973 (Box-folder 16/3)
      p. 36+, article and correspondence
    - "Rain, Rain, Come Today (And Tomorrow, Too)", True's Fishing Yearbook, 1973 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - "Go for Rabbits in Montana", Outdoor Life, January 1973 (Box-folder 16/5)
      p. 38-39
    - "Mexico: Winter Paradise for the American Angler", Field and Stream, February 1973 (Box-folder 16/6)
      p. 170-172+, article and correspondence
    - "Trout: Let 'Em Eat Meat", Sports Afield, March 1973 (Box-folder 16/7)
      p. 11-18, article and correspondence
    - "Wildest Walleyes in the West", Field and Stream, April 1973 (Box-folder 16/8)
      p. 72+, article and correspondence
    - "Car Camping: The First Step", Field and Stream, May 1973 (Box-folder 16/9)
      p. 58-59, article and correspondence
    - "Stretching Your Wader's Life", Field and Stream, May 1973 (Box-folder 16/10)